本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： 闲鱼 黑色风车 魔法莉露姆
校对： 闲鱼  后期： 小安
九点了 你答应我你会回家的
It's nine o'clock, you promised you'd be home.
我知道 我还在市中心 对不起
I know I'm still downtown, I'm sorry.
我们能回家再谈这个吗
Can we talk about this when I get home...
- 求你了  - 你没事吧?
- Please, please... - Are you OK?
- 救命啊 - 约翰
- Help! -  John!
走 进车去
Go, get in!
快走 快走
Let's go, let's go!
卧底游戏 第一季 第七集
你知道 吃饱了再溜出去更容易一点
You know, it's a lot easier to sneak out on a full stomach.
早上好
Good morning.
你不需要每次我们滚床单之后就走的
You don't have to disappear every time we hook up.
吃点早餐也没什么大不了的
A little breakfast never hurt anyone.
除非你是个胆小鬼
Unless you're a chicken.
只是 我习惯早起
It's just that, I have an early morning.
我马上要开会
I got a meeting in a few minutes.
你看 如果我在吃早餐
Look, if I stay for breakfast,
那我就会留下来吃晚餐
then I'll be here for dinner,
也许我们会看场电影 打打台球
and maybe, we'll catch a movie, a ball game.
一个多月之后
A month or so
也许要和你的父母吃晚餐了
and it'll be dinner with your parents...
他们住在亚利桑那
They live in Arizona.
好吧 好吧 也许是和你的老板或者朋友
Okay, fine, then it'll be your boss or a friend.
但是 问题是 我不会去
But, here's the thing, I just won't be there.
- 我做不到 - 玛利亚
- I won't make it. - Maria.
你会假装没事的
And you'll pretend that it's fine
但是你不会相信我
but you won't trust me,
你会开始嫉妒
you'll be jealous.
嘿 嘿 等一下
Hey, hey, come on.
你这是要跟我分手
You're about to break us up
而我们连第一次约会都还没有呢
and we haven't even had our first date yet.
那才是最美妙的
That's the best part.
我是说 我都不知道你是做什么的
I mean, I don't even know what you do for a living.
我喜欢这样
I like this.
伊森 我们俩没事
Ethan, this isn't broken.
你为什么想要修补呢?
Why do you want to fix it?
因为不论你害怕的是什么
Because whatever it is you're scared of,
不要怕我
it's not me.
我们之间 不论是什么
This, whatever this is,
是真的
it's real.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我们跟这个案子已经两周了
We've been on this case two weeks
还有五起劫车案
and there've been five more carjackings.
卡丽
Kelly.
最近一起案件的受害人 约翰・戴维斯
The latest victim. Jon Davis.
两个孩子的父亲 被打的半死
Father of two, beaten unconscious
从最新款的奥迪车上被拖了下来
and relieved of his late model Audi.
我们知道这些案子是有关联的
We know these attacks are related.
他们作案已经有一年的时间了
They go back almost a year.
全城好几个武装的犯罪团伙
Multiple armed crews all over the city.
盗窃汽车案值上千万
Millions of dollars in car thefts.
我们不清楚的是背后的老大是谁
What we don't know is who's calling the shots.
无论是谁在操控这个团伙 运输汽车
Whoever's running the crews and moving the cars,
他们很严谨 是职业的 对吧?
they're serious, they're pros, alright?
袭击无辜平民 极端暴力
Innocent targets, brutal violence.
我们必须马上抓住她们 一定要快
We need to shut these guys down, fast.
你们又进展了?
You've made some progress?
好吧 我一直在接近这两个人
OK, so I've been making friends with these two.
瑞恩和艾利克斯 我在赛车是认识的
Ryan and Alex. I met them at a street race.
- 你赛车? - 你开玩笑呢?
- You were driving? - Are you kidding me?
玛利亚是这个警局最棒的车手
Maria's the best driver in this whole division.
真的?
Seriously?
是的 我爸认为父女的美好时光
Yeah, my dad's idea of quality time
就是让我拿着扭力扳手
was me holding a torque wrench
而他在那换垫圈
while he swapped out a gasket.
那么这些人 他们是搭档吗?
So these guys, are they partners?
是一个两人团伙?
One of the two-men crews?
他们很符合打手的特征
They fit the profile to a T.
是的 艾利克斯是个打手
Yep. Alex has a thug.
他的犯罪记录有一里地长
He's got a rap sheet a mile long.
多次劫车 极端暴力
Plenty of carjacking, brutal violence.
但是瑞恩不一样 他是我要的人
But Ryan's different, he's my guy...
我开车赢过他 聊过两回
I scored points with him driving, talking shop.
他开始信任我
He's starting to trust me and
我可以看出他不喜欢暴力
I can tell he's not into the violence.
他说今天晚点会有活儿
He says he's got a job coming in later today.
有活儿 什么意思?
"Coming in"... What does that mean?
我们不知道 他没有告诉她细节
We don't know. He won't give her the details yet.
但是他答应介绍他们的老大给我认识
But he's agreed to intro me to his boss.
好极了
That's good.
好的 我们给玛利亚做准备吧
A'ight. Let's get Maria prepped.
现在她是我们的首要任务
She's gonna be our primary,
满足她一切的要求
whatever she needs.
这可能是他唯一一次接触到上面的机会
This might be her only chance to move up the chain,
我们不能错过
we can't miss it.
丹尼尔 我希望你能近距离监视
Daniel, I want you close cover.
杰西和我会跟在后面如有必要随时跟进
Jesse and I will hang back and be ready to move where the play takes us.
无论我们要对付的是什么人
Whoever we're dealing with,
他们都是些不择手段的人
has no problem breaking what gets in their way.
所以他们犯罪升级只是个时间问题
So it's only a matter of time until escalates
我们很快要面对的就是凶杀案了
and we end up with a homicide.
从帕萨迪纳的一个家伙
Scooped the cold air intake
手里拿到的冷空气进入口
from a guy in Pasadena.
专门定制打磨
Custom weld and polish.
能让你怎么样? 二十马力 最高了?
And it gets you what? 20 horses, tops?
加入液氮 你可以达到两百
Drop nitrous in and you're talking 200.
时长二十秒 你的引擎也就报废了
For 20 seconds. Then you shred your engine.
让这个巨兽爬到山顶就需要一整箱油
Probably take you a whole tank just to get this beast up a hill.
你需要点新东西
You need something new,
碳纤维 CPU控制的液压系统
carbon fiber, CPU-controlled hydraulics...
当我和别人的车就差一点点时
When I'm red lining into a hairpin,
我相信的是我的车 不是电脑
I trust my car, not a computer.
小心
Watch out.
- 麻烦来了 - 看见了
- Here comes trouble. - I got him.
哥们 你在这干嘛呢?
Watcha doin' here, man?
你知道 我一直搞不懂
You know, I still can't figure out
你这么一个大个子怎么这么怕女生
why a big guy like you is so afraid of girls.
淡定 她没事的
Ease up. She's cool.
瑞恩 我们还有会呢
We have a meet, Ryan.
是吗? 她在这也是为了这个
Yeah? Well, that's why she's here,
我希望她能见见我们的人
I want her to meet our guy.
那有怎样
So what,
你以为你就可以让她进来
you think you just gonna cut her in,
是这意思吗?
is that what you're thinking?
弄的好像这里说的算?
Is that coming out of your cake?
你有问过我吗?
Were you even ask me about that?
就像需要你同意才能行动一样
Like a need your permission to make a move.
我们需要一个开车的她超级棒 你知道的
We need a driver. She's crazy good, you know that.
你现在给我出去马上
You need to get out of here, right now.
否则?
Or what?
相信我 你老板会想见我的
Trust me, your boss is going to want to meet me.
K 别说了 他在这
K, drop it. He's here.
跟你这么说吧 她来我走
I'll tell you what, she's in, I'm out, man.
就这么简单
That simple.
我们以后再谈 行吗?
We'll talk, alright?
好了 好戏开始了
Alright, here we go.
握握手 闲聊两句
It's handshakes and small talk.
熟悉一下建筑和地点
Get familiar with constructions and locations,
你们要的都在那了
everything you need is there.
明白了吗 好的?
Got it, right?
他刚刚给瑞恩一些钱
He just gave Ryan some money.
是的 应该是干这票活儿需要的钱
That's it, that'll be for the job.
我们跟着这家伙
We're gonna stay on this guy.
好的 我们总部见
Alright, I'll see you back at HQ.
他说现在 就是现在 我们今晚行动
He says now, he means now, we do it tonight.
什么活儿?
So what's the gig?
不是吧 你们说过算我一个的
Well, come on. You said you'd cut me in.
- 我还说过让你走的 妞 - 是吗?
- And I told you to disappear, little girl. - Did you?
你知道的 有点怪
You know, it's weird.
你一张嘴我就脑袋就大
I just zone out whenever you open your mouth.
婊子 我让你开开眼怎么样?
How about I make you pay attention, bitch.
嘿 嘿 淡定
Hey, hey, back off.
都冷静点免得有人受伤
Calm down before someone gets hurt.
哦 是吗? 你觉得你能伤到我?
Oh, really? You think you're gonna hurt me?
你是这么想的?
Is that watcha think?
动动我试试
Give me a reason.
啊 哥们 看着她
Arrrgh, get her under control, man.
是的 别激动
Yeah, well, calm down.
你说你需要个开车的 不是吗?
You said you need a driver, right?
宝贝 这不是开礼仪车
This ain't chauffeuring, sweetheart.
我们比一下 你和我 四分之一英里 就现在
Let's go, you, me quarter mile, right now.
我赢了怎么办?
What do I get when I win?
我的车 输了的把车交出来
My ride. We race for pink slips.
玛利亚 你到底在干吗呢?
What the hell are you doing, Maria?
等我把你的车拆了卖了的时候你要在旁边看着
I want you to watch when I sell your car for parts.
你听到了
You heard it.
怎么了? 亲爱的 你需要我让你?
What's wrong? You need a handicap, sweetheart?
我让你两个车身
I'll give you two car length,
但是如果你没种 我的意思是
but if you don't have the balls, I mean...
上车 我不需要你让
Get in your car. I don't need no handicap.
我们把目标人物和
We checked the target's photo
数据库的照片做了比对 没有收获
against the database, nothing.
你查他的车牌了吗?
Did you run his plates?
也没有 你现在在哪?
Also nothing. Where are you right now?
我们跟他到一家店 沃恩赛车
We followed him to a business, Vaughn Motorsports.
- 他还在里面 - 卡莉
- He's still inside. - Kahli?
是一家私人代理商 专做高端汽车
It's a private dealership, exclusive high end car sales.
公司所有人是艾伦和大卫・沃恩
Owned by Ellen and Davin Vaughn.
看起来完全合法
Looks completely legit.
我猜我们必须进店 看一下
I guess we're gonna have to go inside then. Take a look.
你儿子需要辆新车 是这样吗?
Your son needs a new car. Stuff like that?
也许我比较喜欢非正规渠道的东西
Maybe I'm into some kind of sketchy business,
看他们上不上钩
see if they bite.
正合我意
Read my mind.
嘿 如果你能帮我拿到车子
Hey, if you can get me photos of
VIN号码的照片的话
VIN numbers on the cars,
我可以查一下 看是不是偷来的
I can run them, see if they're stolen.
我们就需要一辆就可以申请搜查令
We just need one for a search warrant.
好的 就这么定了
Alright, done.
我们也许该换下衣服
We should probably get changed.
让我们做个有钱人
Let's go get rich.
四分之一英里到达那个水泥路障
Quarter mile to the concrete road block.
第一个到达的胜出
First one there wins.
留着你的车吧
Keep your car.
我只想加入你的行动
All I want is to get in on your action.
好吧
Fine.
今晚来接我们 短信短你
Pick us up tonight. We'll text you.
通常我们只接待预约的顾客
Normally we're by appointment only.
这里的车太炫了
These cars are sick.
他特别迷恋这种东西
He has an exuberance for this sort of thing.
这事真的很急 我忘记了他的生日
This is very last minute, I forgot my son's birthday.
所以我就这么来这讨人嫌了
So I'm in the doghouse here.
你们有什么特别喜欢的吗?
Are you interested in anything in particular?
一个开心儿子
A happy son.
我答应过他想要什么都行
I promised him anything he wanted.
我不知道 他说能吸引靓妞的
I don't know, he said 'chick-magnet'.
我猜是跑车了
I guessing that's a sports car.
嗯 您是
Well, Mr...
罗斯 约翰・罗斯
Ross, John Ross.
你儿子想要什么我们都能帮忙
We can get whatever your son wants.
只要您是认真的
As long as you're serious.
哦 我是认真的
Oh, I'm very serious.
我猜付现金是没问题的
I assume paying cash won't be a problem?
罗斯先生 您是做什么生意的?
What line of work are you in, Mr. Ross?
进出口吧
Let's call it import and export.
现金可以
Cash will be just fine.
好的
Good.
夫妻俩人没有问题
The husband and wife are clean.
我查了每台车的VIN
I ran every VIN number you got and...
没有一辆车是偷来的
Not one of the cars is stolen.
你认为他们还有个改车的地方?
You think they have a chop shop?
应该不是 因为号码印在
No, cause the numbers are stamped
车身的每一个地方 对吧?
all over the parts, right?
所以至少应该有一个会有问题
So one of them would have flagged by now.
他们一定有份参与
They must be involved.
要不那个家伙为什么会在那儿呢?
Why else would this guy be there?
你干嘛呢?
What are you doing?
工作
I'm working.
我们不是在工作吗?
Isn't that what we're doing here?
我不知道 是工作吗?
I don't know, is it?
杰西 丹尼尔在前面等着呢
Jesse, Daniel's waiting out front.
我们去给玛利亚做支援
We're going to back up Maria.
- 快点 - 马上来
- Get moving. - I'm on my way.
我们在这干嘛?
What are we doing here?
我以为我们抢的是车 不是房子
I thought we were breaking into a car, not a house.
你偷过兰博基尼吗?
You ever boosted a Lamborghini?
没有 为什么?
No. Why?
引擎锁定 GPS定位
Engine lock, GPS tracking.
我们要是能拿到钥匙就简单多了也快多了
It's cleaner and faster if we snag the keys.
尤其是家里没有人的时候
Especially when nobody's home.
你确定吗?
You sure about that?
是的 我确定 放心吧
Yeah, I'm sure. Relax.
好了
Gotcha!
我们走吧
Let's do this.
好了 他们进去了 我们看不到
Here we go, they're in. We've got no eyes.
二楼 是他们吗?
Second floor. Is that them?
怎么了?
What's happening?
楼上有灯光 我短信告诉玛利亚
A light just went on upstairs, I'm texting Maria.
有人在家
伙计们
Guys.
我听到楼上有人 有人在家
I heard someone upstairs. Someone's home.
我们得马上走
We gotta go.
也许我们应该等等
Maybe we should bail?
不 不 没车我们不走
No, no, we don't leave without the car.
有人吗?
Is someone there?
你他妈的在干吗?
What the hell are you doing?
嘿 不要!
Hey, no!
进去! 快!
Get in there! Go!
你真不该下来 老家伙
You should have stayed upstairs, old man.
够了! 住手
Enough! Stop.
我说了 住手!
I said stop!
后退! 他看到你脸了
Back off! He saw your face.
我们得干掉他
We have to deal with him.
我们可不是来这儿惹麻烦的
We're not here to make a mess.
我们的目标是车
We're here for the car.
警察! 举起手来!
Police! Show me your hands!
趴到地上 地上! 趴下!
Get on the ground. On the ground! Get down!
- 举起手! - 趴下!
- Show me your hands! - Get down!
先生 你没事吧?
Sir, you alright?
你不会有事的 先生
You're going to be alright, sir.
来辆救护车到派尔德街二十号
I need an ambulance at 20 Peldar Street.
伤者是男性公民 头部受到重创
I have a civilian male, severe head trauma.
我也不是第一次遇到这种情况
This isn't my first time either,
所以不用跟我这儿来硬汉那一套
so you can skip the tough guy stuff.
- 我们都是专家 对吧? - 专家?
- We're both professionals, right? - Professionals?
职业警察 职业罪犯
Career cop, career criminal.
是什么就是什么
It is what it is.
随你怎么说
Whatever you say.
跟我说说你的老板
I need an introduction to your boss.
为什么? 能让我少坐几年牢
For what? Maybe a couple years off my sentence?
还是让我早点假释?
Maybe some early parole?
我可以跟起诉人谈谈
I can talk to the prosecutor.
是吗? 听起来不错
Yeah? That sounds good.
但是 我可不是告密者
Except, I ain't no rat.
我能熬过去 狗娘养的
I can stand my time, bitch.
所以去你的吧
So screw you.
那我就放心了
Well, I have to say that's a relief.
菲尔・布伦特 房子里那男的
Phil Bronte, the man at the house.
你把个老人家打伤了 艾利克斯
You put a grandfather in the hospital, Alex.
你失控了 你是个懦夫
You're out of control, and you're a coward.
我之前还担心你会达成交易呢
I was worried you might cut a deal.
你玩儿我呢吧?
You tryin' to play me?
没有
No games.
实际上
Truth is,
我想让你坐很长
I want you to go to jail for a long,
很长时间的牢
long time.
而你刚才的不合作
And this non-compliance you're showing,
意味着我可以给你加到最长刑期
that means I can push for maximum sentence.
真是美好的一天
It's a good day.
最大量刑 你说真的?
Maximum sentence, are you serious in there?
没开玩笑
It was no play.
重案组可以起诉他 让他们好好考虑
Major crime can charge him. Make sure they take their time.
- 好 - 那现在呢?
- OK. - So what now?
我们继续跟着瑞恩?
We stick with Ryan?
让他成为线人
Make him an agent,
看看他会不会跟我们合作 是吗?
see if he'll work with us, maybe?
玛利亚?
Maria?
我们需要瑞恩的帮助
We're going to need Ryan's help,
他可以让我们接触到齐克
he can get us to Zeke.
你觉得他能行吗?
Think he can handle it?
我不知道
I don't know.
你不觉得他会跟我们吗?
You don't think he'll flip?
差不多
In a heart beat.
这次真的吓到他了 他不想干了
This just got real for him. He needs an out.
但和我们共事压力很大
But working with us is a lot of pressure.
我不确定能不能信任他
I'm not sure I can trust him.
好吧 那么你何不进去
OK, so why don't you go in there,
和他聊聊 感觉一下
talk to him, see how it feels.
好吧 我试一下
Okay. I'll give it a shot.
他状态不太好
He's in rough shape.
- 能让我们单独谈谈吗? - 行
- Can you give us the room? - Yeah.
好的
All right.
嘿瑞恩
Hey, Ryan.
你是警察? 逗我呢吧?
You're a cop? Are you kidding me?
你真行 我一点儿都没看出来
You're good, I had no idea.
特傻的是我居然很高兴见到你
You know what's stupid? I'm still happy to see you.
见到朋友总是好的
It's always good to see a friend.
可你是警察
You're a cop.
也是你现在最好的朋友
Best friend to have right now.
那又如何...?
So what...?
你打算 比如 审问我吗?
Are you going to, like, question me?
打个报告? 送我坐牢?
Make a report? Take me to jail?
我有得选吗?
Do I have a choice?
每个人都会犯错 你就是我犯的错
Everybody makes mistakes, you're mine.
我妈老跟我这么说
My mom always said that to me.
这对孩子来说真是句恶毒无比的话
That's a hell of a thing to say to her kid.
是啊 但我又做了些什么
Yeah, but what I'm doing,
偷车还有所有那些...?
stealing cars and all that...?
她恨我这样
She hates it.
我不怪她
I don't blame her.
看看我这幅样子
Look at me.
坐在这儿满脑子都是我妈会怎么想
I'm sitting here worrying what my mom's gonna think.
昨晚
Last night,
你试着阻止艾利克斯
you tried to stop Alex.
- 他在打那个人... - 所以呢?
- He was beating that man... - So?
所以你知道我怎么想的吗?
So you know what I think?
我觉得你不是那种人
I think you're better than that.
你比他好
Than him.
我可以帮你
I can help you.
我可以撤销对你的指控 但你必须先帮我
I can drop these charges but you have to help me first.
你想让我怎么帮你?
What kind of help are we talkin'?
让我加入组织
I need a way in.
要从昨天那家伙开始 那是你的老板吧?
We'll start with the guy from yesterday, your boss?
然后顺线上去...
Work our way up...
嘿 如果你做不来 你要告诉我
Hey, if you aren't up for this, you need to let me know.
我要确定能否
I need to be able to trust you.
完全信任你
Completely.
我能信任你吗?
Can I trust you?
先告诉我你头儿的名字
Let's start with the name of your boss.
开悍马的那家伙 他给了你工作
The guy in the Hummer who gave you the job.
告诉我你在为谁干活?
Why don't you tell me who you work for?
他叫齐克・温斯顿
His name is Zeke Weston.
他非常暴躁
He's crazy violent.
尤其当你犯错的时候
Especially if you make a mistake.
雇佣着大概十帮人来偷车
Runs, like, ten crews of guys who jack cars.
他给我们姓名和地址
He gives us a name, an address,
我们负责送车
we deliver the cars,
而齐克则负责把车弄干净并合法化
and Zeke makes them squeaky clean and legal.
之后呢? 怎么卖掉?
What happens to them then? How do they get sold?
客户知道这些车是偷来的吗?
Do the clients know they're stolen?
我发誓我不知道
I swear, I have no idea.
我只是个助手 好吧?
I'm just the help, right?
而且齐克口风很紧
And Zeke isn't much of a talker.
你能让我作为你的新搭档入伙吗
Can you bring me in as your new partner?
他会同意吗?
You think he'd go for that?
可以
Yeah.
我是说
I mean,
我可以试试
I can try.
好 那我们这就进入齐克的车库
OK, so we're going right into Zeke's garage,
鉴于你昨晚被抓了
with you getting busted last night,
他现在估计正急的要死
he's gonna be tense as hell.
所以你要让他冷静下来
So you got to keep him calm,
让他觉得局面还在他掌控之中 知道吗?
he needs to feel like he's in control, alright?
我兄弟们就在外面
Now my guys will be outside,
他们会听到我们的对话
they'll be listening.
所以如果我们遇到麻烦
So if we get into any kind of trouble,
他们会来救我们
they'll be right there to back us up.
那么你准备好了吗?
Okay, you ready?
深呼吸 记住"我不是警察"
Take a deep breath. And remember, "I'm not a cop."
走吧
Come on.
她来这儿干嘛?
What the hell is she doing here?
啊?
Huh?
问你话呢 她在这儿干嘛?
I asked you a question. What is she doing here?
加油瑞恩 走近些 你能行
Come on, Ryan. Step up. You got this.
你昨晚给我们派的任务
That job you gave us last night.
把我们坑惨了齐克
That was junk, Zeke.
那家伙在家呢好吗?
The guy was home, alright?
艾利克斯完蛋了
Alex is done.
是啊 艾利克斯给我打电话了
Yeah, Alex called me.
从监狱里 他说你被抓了
From jail. He said you got busted.
没错 我保释了自己 老兄
That's right, I had to bail myself out, man.
艾利克斯重打了那家伙所以他还在牢里
Alex beat the hell out of the guy which is why he's still in.
无论如何 关键是我现在需要个新搭档
Anyway, the point is, now I need a new partner.
行吗?
Alright?
这就是为什么带她来
That's what she's doing here.
我只是想和你交代清楚
I just wanted to clear it with you,
表示我对你的尊敬
out of respect.
瑞恩有时候会犯糊涂
Ryan gets very confused sometimes.
说些不该说的话
He says things he shouldn't.
你们在哪儿认识的?
Where'd you meet her?
我叫玛利亚
It's Maria.
在谢丽海滩赛车的时候
Racing pink slips out at Cherry Beach.
她会开车?
She can drive?
让他六个车身 依然超不了我
Gave him a spot, six car lengths. Still smoked him.
她给谁干活?
Who does she work for?
你 从现在开始
You. Starting now.
加油 加油...
Come on. Come on...
没你事儿了 招人我说了算
We're done here. I do the recruiting.
走吧
Take a walk.
没成
No sale.
没事
It's alright.
也算是迈出了第一步 我们先盯着齐克
Could be a first step, we'll stay on Zeke.
看看他去哪儿
See what he gets into.
不得不说这真个惊喜
I have to say I'm impressed.
这个车型只有五百辆
Only five hundred production models built,
而上次我来的时候还没有呢
and last time I checked there weren't any left.
你在哪儿找到的?
Where did you find it?
从一些供应商那里
I have a number of suppliers.
我能拍张照片吗?
You mind if I take a photograph?
给我儿子看看
For my son.
现在要是没有照片为证
These days if it doesn't happen in a photograph,
就等同于不存在
it never happened.
当然可以
Of course.
好的 收到照片
Ok, got the photo.
你觉得你儿子会喜欢它吗?
Do you think your son will like it?
希望喽 这可是他最喜欢的颜色
I hope so. It's his favorite color.
不是 车子没问题
Nothing. It's clean.
我有个海外的朋友 他对这类东西很感兴趣
I have friends overseas who'd be interested in this sort of thing.
- 是吗? - 当然 但必须得是批量的
- Is that right? - Of course, it would have to be volume.
可如果你能搞来这样的车
But if you could move cars like this,
两万一辆怎么样?
20 grand a unit?
两万英镑一辆?
20 thousands each?
能卖出这价格那只能是偷来的车
At that price they would have to be stolen.
你能搞来这样的货?
You have the capacity for this sort of operation?
我从海外用集装箱运来
I ship things overseas, in containers.
大型机械 纺织品之类的
Heavy machinery, textiles, that sort of thing.
也包括车
Including cars.
当然有可能 为什么不呢?
Certainly possible, why not?
你找错人了 罗斯先生
You're talking to the wrong people, Mr. Ross.
那太遗憾了
That's too bad.
很抱歉我们没法儿帮您
I'm sorry we can't help you.
但如果你想通了
Well, if you change your mind.
我会给我儿子看这照片
I'm going to show this to my son.
随时可以联系我
I'll be in touch.
祝福你儿子
Give our best to your boy.
又查了一遍 VIN码是合法的
Once again, VIN was clean.
但他们肯定在做假
Nah, they've gotta be fake.
卡丽查了那编号 文件是合法的
Khali ran the numbers. Paperwork's legit.
我要的是一辆不可能买到的车
I ask for a car that's impossible to buy,
他们却一夜之间给搞来了
and they come up with one literally overnight.
那我们也无法证明它是偷来的
We have no way to prove that it's stolen.
是啊 但他的妻子艾伦
Yeah, but the wife, Ellen,
她对这笔买卖感兴趣
she was into the deal.
她已经在盘算如何花赚来的钱了
She was already spending the money in her head.
就是说她丈夫反倒退缩了?
It was the husband that backed away?
这里面肯定有问题 气氛异常紧张
There was something going on there, plenty of tension.
那些人很谨慎 从齐克那儿就能看出来
These people are careful, we've seen that with Zeke.
他们很聪明 所以我们只能更聪明
They're smart, so we just have to be smarter.
- 是啊 - 是丹尼尔
- Yeah - It's Daniel.
- 嘿 -齐克这边有动静了
- Hey. - We've got action with Zeke.
我们跟着他来到一个公园 他下车了
We followed him to a park. He's out of his car.
他在干嘛?
What's he doing?
像是来见那个妻子 艾伦・沃恩
Looks like he's meeting up with the wife, Ellen Vaughn.
只有她吗? 丈夫没来?
Just her? No husband?
看样子是的
Yeah, looks that way.
哇哦 你看到那幕了吗?
Whoa, are you seeing this?
看到了 继续拍照
Yeah, keep shooting.
- 看到什么? -艾伦和齐克
- What is it? - Ellen and Zeke.
我想我们找到打入的办法了
I think we just found a way in.
就是说她嫁给了有钱人
So she's married to the money,
却在和他的打手偷腥
but she's sleeping with the muscle.
是啊 这可绝非一夜情那么简单
Yeah, this is more than a one night stand.
- 你确定? - 确定 看他的手
- You're sure? - Yeah, look at his hand.
在她背上 他们之间很亲密 不是一时的
On her back, there's a closeness between them, not an urgency.
她看他的眼神里体现了信任
She's looking into his eyes. There's trust there.
她动情了
This is real for her.
那我们能如何利用这件事?
So how do we use it?
我去和艾伦谈谈
I'll reach out to Ellen.
如果她想和她男朋友远走高飞
If she's looking for an exit ramp for her and her boyfriend,
我很乐意提供帮助
I'll be happy to provide.
同时让瑞恩把照片寄给她丈夫
Meanwhile, Ryan delivers the photos to the husband.
他想证明自己的忠诚
He wants to prove his loyalty,
并且觉得大卫应该知道他妻子干了些什么
and thought Davin should know what his wife is doing.
他会利用这个机会往上爬
He uses it as a chance to step up.
瑞恩压力很大
That's a lot of pressure on Ryan.
他能对付
He can handle it.
和艾伦约见 看看她买不买账
Set up a meeting with Ellen, see if she bites.
好的
All right.
- 嘿 那孩子的事儿干得漂亮 -瑞恩吗?
- Hey. Nice job with this kid. - Ryan?
任何人都能说服他
Anyone could've flipped him.
不是那样的
That's not true.
你真的打动他了
You made a genuine connection.
他信任你玛利亚
He trusts you, Maria,
他对你坚信不疑
he believes in you.
他看我的时候 只是看到不用坐牢的机会
He looks at me, all he sees is a get out of jail free card.
别这么武断
Don't be so sure.
我们等你的信号
We're just waiting on a signal.
你还记得该怎么说吗?
You remember what to say?
我是你的新搭档 对吗... ?
I'm your new partner, right... ?
没错 我知道了
Yeah. I'm good.
我会和你保持距离 交给你了
I'm gonna keep my distance, you got this.
在没会开车就已经偷了第一辆车
I jacked my first car before I could drive.
我跟一个兄弟 我们偷了这辆面包车
Me and a buddy, we swiped this minivan,
开着它绕过街区
drove it around the block.
一定很爽了
I bet it was a rush.
虽然听起来很傻
It sounds stupid
但我总觉得我做不好那件事
but I always thought I wouldn't be able to do it.
就像它绝不会那么容易或者之类的
Like it wouldn't be that easy or something.
然后我开始研究安保系统
Then I started learning security systems,
点火倍率
ignition overrides.
只要有发动机的东西我都能弄来
I could boost anything with an engine.
我们通常从机场停车场偷车
We used to swipe cars from the airport lot.
没有人受伤
No one got hurt.
仿佛一切都不是真的
It's like it wasn't even real.
但是这些家伙...
But these guys...
每个人都受伤了
Everyone gets hurt.
我们会阻止这种事发生
We'll shut them down.
我经常觉得警察都是没用的东西
I always thought cops were kind of lame.
但是现在呢?
But all this?
可比驾着面包车兜风刺激多了
Way bigger rush than joyriding that minivan.
我猜你差不多已经习惯了
I guess you're probably used to it.
从不会厌倦
It never gets old.
但也不容易
It's gotta be tough, though.
总是假装成其他人
Always pretending to be someone you're not.
你有怀念过做自己的时候吗?
You ever just miss just being yourself?
- 喂 - 你该出发了
- Yeah. - You're good to go.
好的 马上出发
Okay. Headed in.
准备好了吗?
You ready?
嗯
Yeah...
真是散步的好日子
It's a nice day for a walk.
我很高兴你能给我打电话
I'm glad you called.
我想替我丈夫向你道歉
I wanted to apologize for my husband.
你不必道歉 我理解
You don't have to apologize, I understand.
他太霸道了 控制欲极强
He's the overbearing, controlling type.
你这么觉得吗?
Is that what you think?
我来告诉你我都知道些什么
I'll tell you what's clear to me.
你们根本不合拍 如果我是你
Your partnership isn't working and if I were you,
我会甩了他
I'd ditch him.
我能帮你运车艾伦
I can move your cars, Ellen.
这是一个错误
This was a mistake.
艾伦 你是这里最聪明的人
Ellen, you're the smartest person in the room
他却不相信你的判断
and he won't even trust your judgment.
我来这儿 并不是要听人评说我的婚姻的
I didn't come here for an appraisal of my marriage.
你已经取得完全自治权了  你会得到产品
You'll have complete autonomy, you'll obtain the product,
我会移民国外 然后卖掉它
I'll move it overseas, where I will sell it.
你真的知道我在做什么生意吗?
What kind of business do you think I'm running, exactly?
你难道以为我是无缘无故碰巧出现吗?
Look, do you think I just happened to come out of nowhere?
我关注你的生意已经有段日子了
I've had my eyes on your operation for some time now.
只要你需要
I can help you
我能帮你把它上升到一个新的水平
take it to another level if you want me to.
这由你决定
It's up to you.
- 沃恩先生 - 你是瑞恩 对吗?
- Mr. Vaughn. - Ryan, isn't it?
齐克不在这里
Zeke's not here.
其实 先生 我想跟你谈谈
Actually, sir, I wanted to talk to you.
我想见你 是因为
The reason I wanted to see you...
瑞恩 不管是什么事 你可以跟齐克说
Ryan, whatever it is, you can take it up with Zeke.
你得离开这儿
You need to leave now.
- 这对他来说太难了 - 再给他点时间
- This is too much for him. - Give him a second.
他把照片拿出来了
Photos just went down.
没人知道 我发誓
No one knows. I swear.
为什么给我这些?
Why bring this to me?
齐克已经难以控制了 他很危险
Zeke is out of control, he's dangerous.
整个运作应该是干净利索 低调行事
This operation should be clean, low profile.
但是齐克的手下总是下重手
But Zeke's got crews putting people in hospitals.
如果我搭档和我能回去 我们不会这样的
Me and my partner back there, we'll do things differently.
所以你想要这份工作 你是个投机主义者
So you want his job. You're an opportunist.
如果我是 我会敲诈你太太
If I was, I'd be blackmailing your wife.
他做得很好
He's doing good.
听好 我明白 我对你来说一文不值
Look, I get it. I'm nobody to you, I'm nothing.
但是现在 我是唯一不会对你说谎的人
But right now, I'm the one person who isn't lying to you.
等等
Wait.
今晚再来 我要跟你谈谈
Come back tonight, we'll talk.
我还以为他不会去拿呢
I thought for sure he wasn't gonna go for it.
- 你做的很棒 - 我们下一步要干嘛?
- You did great in there. - So what's our next move?
我们刚刚摧毁了他们整个的合作基础
We just blew up their entire foundation.
现在 我们要让大卫看到
Now, we show Davin that
我们能帮他重建这一切
we can help put it back together.
貌似瑞恩干得很不错啊
Looks like Ryan made quite the impression.
车行已经关门了
The dealership was shut up tight.
没看见大卫也没看见那对爱情鸟
No sign of Davin or the lovers.
大卫现在一定吓坏了
I'm sure Davin is freaking out right now.
他说会保持联系
He said he'd be in touch.
嘿 看 我弄了些东西
Hey, look at this, I got something.
我替约翰的进出口公司做了个假冒的网站
I set up a fake website for John's import-export firm.
艾伦・沃恩刚刚查看了这个网站
Ellen Vaughn just paid it a visit.
你确信是艾伦?
You sure it's Ellen?
没错 我追踪了那个IP地址 就是她
Yeah, I tracked the IP address, it's her,
她正在调查他
she's checking him out.
这表示她很感兴趣
That means she's interested.
她要有所行动了
She's making a move.
她跟齐克 很好 他们斗成一团
Her and Zeke, that's good. They're scrambling.
如果我们能够成交一次 就能停止这一切
If we could set up a buy we could shut this whole thing down.
哦不 是瑞恩 出了点事 他很惊慌
Oh no, it's Ryan. Something's wrong, he's panicking.
我得走了
I gotta go.
我收到短信了 出什么事了?
I got your text, what's wrong?
我们搞砸了
We messed up.
齐克给我打了电话 他听上去很奇怪
Zeke called me. He sounds really weird.
大卫一定告诉他我出卖了他
Davin must have told him that I ratted him out.
好的 慢慢讲 告诉我到底发生了什么
OK, slow down. Tell me what happened.
齐克想让我从接头点接手一辆车
Zeke wants me to pick up a car from the drop spot,
把一切都弄好
get it taken care of.
- 什么意思? - 我为他做过一次
- What does that mean? - I did this once for him.
如果我们弄到一辆特别扎手的车
If we get a car that's too hot,
齐克就会把它留在接头点 等我去拿
Zeke leaves it in the drop spot for me.
我去接车 送去报废
I have to pick it up, take it to the crushers.
所以一旦你被抓住 都是你自己的责任
So if you get busted with the car, it's on you,
齐克就躲得远远的
and Zeke just walks away.
通常这没什么  但这次 事情不一样
It's usually no big deal. But this time, something's different.
从他的声音里我能听出来  冷冰冰的
I could hear it in his voice. He was ice-cold.
你觉得他给你下套了?
You think he's setting you up?
那个接头点很偏僻 没有安装摄像头
The drop spot is isolated, there's no cameras.
如果我去了那里 什么事都可能发生
If I go there, anything could happen.
但我们别无选择
But we don't have a choice.
如果我们不按照齐克说的去做
Zeke will get suspicious
他就会起疑的 是吗?
if we don't do what he says, right?
"我们?"
"We?"
你不用一个人做这事 接头点在哪?
You're not alone in this. Where's the pickup spot?
- 在那条路 - 走吧
- It's back that way. - Let's go.
我的伙计们会来 我们会检查那辆车
Here come my guys. We're gonna check out the car,
确保是安全的
make sure it's safe.
嘿 就呆在那儿
Hey, stay back.
我们绕着这里转了两遍 没问题 只有我们
We circled the perimeter twice, it's clear. We're alone.
好的 那辆车?
Alright, which one?
就在那儿 那辆红色轿车
Right there, red sedan.
钥匙在保险杠下面
Keys are under the bumper.
我觉得不对劲
It doesn't look right to me.
后轮压得很低 后备箱一定有重物
The back wheels are low. There's something heavy in the trunk.
丽贝卡 我们看到了那辆车
Rebecca, we got eyes on the car,
可能安装了爆炸物
could be rigged with explosives.
让所有人离开现场 我立刻让防爆小组过去
Get everyone out of there, I'm calling the bomb squad.
哦不 等等 虽然齐克很鲁莽
Oh, no, wait a second, we know Zeke is reckless
做事不计后果
and impulsive.
但是...炸弹? 这说不通
But... a bomb? It doesn't make sense.
尤其 如果这是私人恩怨
Especially if it's personal.
如果要报复
If anything,
他想的也是用撬棍砸烂瑞恩的脑袋
he's going to want to cave Ryan's head in with a tire iron himself.
我要到近处去看看
I'm going to take a closer look.
约翰 你在听我说吗? 不要靠近那里
John, are you listening to me? Keep your distance.
丽贝卡 我听不清你说话 信号不好
Rebecca, I'm losing you, you're starting to break up.
马上派紧急行动组去那里 除爆小组
Roll ETF to their location now. Bomb disposal unit.
- 你要干嘛? - 我要去看看
- What are you doing? - I'm gonna go take a look.
我跟你一起
I'm right with you.
不不不 你们俩都别动
No, no, no. Both of you stay put.
我们之间只要有一个傻大胆就够了
Only need one of us to be stupid.
约翰!
John!
凶杀组正在申请搜查令
Homicide's working on search warrants.
太慢了
Too slow.
这会儿功夫 那对爱情鸟已经飞走了
In the meantime, our happy couple disappears.
我们没时间了 我们需要拿到供认书
We're running out of time, we need to get a confession.
好消息是 艾伦・沃恩已经出手了
The good news is Ellen Vaughn has reached out.
她想要跟出口商约翰・罗斯 见面
She wants a meeting with John Ross, the exporter.
所以我们两头出击
So we do a double play.
我和妻子谈的时候
While I'm working on the wife,
玛利亚也在努力拿下男朋友齐克
Maria could be working on the boyfriend, Zeke.
我们得弄一辆和发现尸体的那辆
We gotta get a matching car, same make, model
款式相同 型号相同
as the one we found the body in.
- 为什么? - 这样瑞恩就能把它开回去
- Why? - So that Ryan can drive it back.
他太紧张了 看了一眼后备箱
He got nervous, he looked in the trunk,
发现了尸体
found the body.
现在他去见齐克 害怕的要命
Now he's gonna confront Zeke, all freaked out.
看到那辆车 受到如此惊吓...
Seeing that car, the shock of it...
他们就会分崩离析
They might just fall apart.
是啊 这计划不错
Yeah, that's a good plan.
但这样他们就会坦白吗?
But does it get us a confession?
这时候 也是我们最好的机会了
At this point, it's our best shot.
好 我们已经就位了
Okay, we're in position.
- 太好了玛利亚? -准备好了
- Good. Maria? - Good to go.
随时候命 我们要等约翰的指令
Stand by, we're waiting on John's signal.
好的 随时候命
Okay, standing by.
随时行动
Any minute now.
我不知道齐克看到这辆车会作何反应
Look, we don't know how Zeke's gonna react when he sees this car.
我知道
I do.
我来做 我知道该怎么跟他说
I got this, I know how to talk to him.
如果事情变糟 你就听我指令
If things go South, you follow my lead.
好
Yeah.
等这一切都过去了 你觉得你会做什么?
When this is all over with, you ever thought about what you might do?
除了偷车 我什么也不会
I've never been good at anything besides stealing cars.
你这件事就做的很棒
You're pretty good at this.
我不是警察
I'm no cop.
不 但是我们可以给你开工资 你可以帮我们
No. But we could put you on the payroll, and you could help us out.
把这当一份工作吗?
As a job?
是的 你很擅长
Yeah, you're pretty good at this.
可能会很值得
Might be worth it,
想象我妈脸上骄傲的表情就知道了
just to see the look on my mom's face.
我们必须马上运走这些车子 要快
We want to move the cars, right now, fast.
都准备好了 明细单就放在我办公室
They're all ready to go, the detailed list is in my office.
我不需要明细单
I don't need a list.
我只需要知道每辆车的来历
What I need is the history of each vehicle.
以免任何问题发生
In case any issues should arise.
不会有任何问题 我亲自检查过
They're untraceable. I do the work myself.
这可不能保证
That's not much of an assurance.
我的顾客需要的可不是这个
My clients need more than that.
我们记下了那些废车的车辆识别代码
We take the VIN numbers from wrecked cars,
然后拷贝了一份 放在我们的车上
we copy them, and we put them on ours.
但是那就没有书面记录了
But then there's no paper trail.
我们做了一份
We make one.
你可以尽管调查
You can look as deep as you want,
但你只会发现这些车没问题
all you find is a clean car.
我们可以在办公室谈价钱
We can discuss money in my office.
那是当然 但我想先给我儿子挑份礼物
Of course. But first I want to pick up that present for my son.
- 信号来了  -玛利亚 该你上了
- There's the cue.  - Maria, you're on.
我们拿到他们偷车的证据了
We've got them on the cars,
现在该找他们谋杀的证据了
now let's get them for murder.
好的 现在就去
OK, going in.
没事吧?
Is everything okay?
没事
Fine.
我们去办公室吧
Let's step into my office.
给我把它弄走
Get that out of here.
车 还是后备箱的尸体?
The car, or the body in the  trunk?
你丈夫会跟我们一起吗?
Will your husband be joining us?
不 这事我来处理
No I'll be handling this.
我只想知道他是否会带来麻烦
All I need to know is if he's gonna be a problem.
我们能给他打电话吗?
Can we get him on the phone?
不行 他没空
I can't, he's unavailable.
你怎么打算的?
What was the plan?
我扔车时被抓 然后被判谋杀?
I get caught dumping the car, go down for murder?
是这样吗? 你真的觉得你能跑得掉?
Was that it? Did you really think you could get away with it?
你根本不知道自己在说什么
You don't know what you're talking about.
是吗? 那告诉我吧
Yeah...? So tell me.
你马上给我闭嘴 然后滚出去
You need to shut up, right now. Move. Outside.
来吧瑞恩 我们出去吧
Come on, Ryan, let's go outside.
你会像杀了大卫一样杀掉我吗?
So you gonna kill me like you killed Davin, huh?
你这个懦夫
You coward?
瑞恩 够了
Ryan, that's enough.
丹尼尔, 杰西, 你们上
Daniel, Jesse, start moving in.
走吧
Let's go.
好了瑞恩 我们走吧
Come on, Ryan, let's go.
你不该来这里
You shouldn't have come here.
告诉我到底发生了什么事
Tell me what happened,
不然我就去报警
or else I'm going to the cops.
瑞恩 别说了!
Ryan, stop!
我跟你说闭嘴!
I told you to shut up!
瑞恩! 不...
Ryan! No...
约翰 他有刀 快过来!
John, he's got a knife, get over here!
警察已经到了 别动!
Police get on the ground, don't move!
流了好多血
There's so much blood.
我需要一辆救护车到 杜梅路151号
I need an ambulance at 151 Dumay,
有人受伤了
we have a civilian injured.
- 严重的腹部刺伤 - 别叫了!
- Severe abdominal stab. - Shut up!
瑞恩 听我说
Ryan, listen to me, listen.
你要保持冷静 好吗 救护车马上就来了
You have to stay still, okay. Ambulance is on it's way.
这发生的太快了
It happened so fast.
我知道 看着我 看着我
I know, look at me, look at me.
现在想像你告诉妈妈你为警察工作的时候
I want you to picture your mom's face
你妈妈的表情
when you tell her you work for the cops.
她不会相信的
She'd never believe me.
你会没事的 你会挺过去的 知道吗?
You're gonna be OK, you're gonna get out of this, OK?
救护车就快来了瑞恩!
The ambulance is on it's way. Ryan!
瑞恩瑞恩 你会没事的
Ryan, Ryan, you're gonna be okay.
我甚至不知道你的真名
I don't even know your real name.
我叫玛利亚 玛利亚・科尔特斯.
It's Maria. Maria Cortez.
真是美丽的名字啊
That's a really pretty name.
没事的 你会好起来的
It's okay, you're going to be okay.
瑞恩 别动求你了
Ryan, stay still, please.
求你了
Please..!
我叫玛利亚 是一名警察
My name is Maria, I'm a police officer.
我想跟你谈谈你儿子的事瑞恩
I need to talk to you about your son, Ryan.
你们这些人
You people.
不知道 我不知道他在哪里
No, I don't know where he's living,
我也好几年都没跟他说过话了
and no, I haven't talked to him in a couple of years.
呃 埃伍德太太 瑞恩并没惹什么麻烦
Uh, Mrs. Everwood. Ryan isn't in trouble.
他之前在帮警察处理一件案子
He was working on a case, helping police.
帮我
Helping me.
帮助我
瑞恩受伤了 他被人刺了几刀
Ryan's been injured, he was stabbed.
有多严重?
How bad is it?
他流了很多血
He lost a lot blood,
马上就要做手术
he's gonna need surgery,
但他还很清醒 而且...
but he is conscious, and...
医生也认为他会没事的
The doctors think he's gonna be okay.
我就知道迟早会这样 我一直等着这一天到来
I knew this was gonna happen, I've been waiting for it.
你的儿子拯救了很多人 让他们免于受伤
Your son stopped a lot of people from getting hurt.
他想要改变
He wants to make a change.
他想见你
He's been asking for you.
如果你愿意 我可以带你去
I can take you if you'd like.
好的 谢谢
Yes, thank you.
怎么了?
What?
玛利亚很自责
Maria's blaming herself.
那孩子差点就死了
That kid almost died.
她会没事的 我会跟她谈谈
She'll be fine. I'll check in with her.
这种工作
This job.
你一直以来跟某个人来往 然后...
You spend all this time with someone and then...
你逮捕他们 或者...
You arrest them, or...
他们会被刺伤...
They get stabbed...
但是你已经跟他们产生感情了
But you made a connection.
你对他们敞开心扉
You opened up to them.
你知道什么最难吗?
You know what the tough part is?
晚上回到家 面对爱你的人
Going home at night to someone who loves you,
你必须向他们坦白
and you have to open up to them,
再一次坦白所有的事情
all over again.
- 抱歉我没事先打电话 - 没关系
- I'm sorry I didn't call first. - No, it's okay.
我是个警察
I'm a cop.
你曾经好奇过我的职业
You wanted to know what I do for a living.
是的
Okay.
而且你错了
And you were wrong.
我很害怕你
I am scared of you.
长久以来 你是第一个让我有感觉的人
You're the first guy I've connected with, in a long time.
这让我有点害怕
And that kind of freaks me out.
嘿...
Hey...
为什么不进来呢?
Why don't you come inside?
我们出去吧
Let's go out.
聊聊
Talk.
现在是早上三点
It's three in the morning.
没关系
That's okay.
你会习惯的
You'll get used to it.